Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
5582
Kheel Center
80.1 linear ft.
Pamphlets.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The Archives Foreign File is a collection of printed ephemeral documents, issued primarily by foreign and international trade unions and labor organizations. All continents are represented, though the majority of materials is of European origin. Topics covered in this collection include union organizing, unemployment, working conditions, the working class, the labor movement, industrial relations, worker education, international trade unionism, works councils, automation, economic conditions and trends, labor markets, foreign relations, and political movements, including fascism, socialism, and communism. Included in this collection are materials on the World Confederation of Labor and the World Federation of Trade Unions.
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into four sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Section 4: Boxes 67-79
Boxes 80-81 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
Subjects:
Labor unions; Labor unions--Political activity; Labor unions and foreign policy; Labor movement; International labor activities; Working class; Working class--Education; Industrial relations; Labor market; Unemployment; Economic history; Works councils; Work environment; Management--Employee participation; International relations; Labor unions and communism; Labor unions and socialism; Labor unions and fascism; Industrial safety; Industrial hygiene; Communism; Fascism; Socialism; Automation
Form and Genre Terms:
Pamphlets
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other parts of this Collection:
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF)
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1: Boxes 1-22
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2: Boxes 23-44
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Boxes 80-82 have not been inventoried at this point.
CONTAINER LIST
- Box: 67, Folder: 1 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Cultural activities of Soviet trade unions, 1945; Publication (Box 67, Folder 1)
    Author: Ilya Tsaregradsky
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- Box: 67, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: German workers in the Soviet Union, 1932; Publication (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Box: 67, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The heroes of Grozny, 1932; Publication (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Box: 67, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: How workers become engineers in the U.S.S.R., 1932; Publication (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Author: V. Druzhinin
- Box: 67, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The October revolution and the trade unions, 1933; Publication (Box 67, Folder 5)
    Author: Ans Kristalovich Abolin
- Box: 67, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Reorganization of the work of the trade unions, 1934; Publication (Box 67, Folder 6)
    Author: N.M. Shvernik
- Box: 67, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Speech of welcome to foreign delegates, 1933; Publication (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Box: 67, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Stakhanov movement and the cultural growth of the working class, 1935; Publication (Box 67, Folder 8)
    Author: Vyacheslav Mikhaylovich Molotov
- Box: 67, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Thomas Monger and Johann Liebhardt, 1932; Publication (Box 67, Folder 9)
    Author: S. Besborodov
- Box: 67, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The trade unions, the party and the state, 1927; Publication (Box 67, Folder 10)
    Author: M.P. Tomskii
- Box: 67, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Unemployment in the USSR and the struggle against it, 1927; Publication (Box 67, Folder 11)
    Author: A. Katz
- Box: 67, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Where the workers are in power, 1931; Publication (Box 67, Folder 12)
    Author: David Losifovich Zaslavskii
- Box: 67, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Who is the boss of the factory?, 1965; Publication (Box 67, Folder 13)
    Author: Gennadii Kovalev
- Box: 67, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Why piece work in the U.S.S.R.?, 1932; Publication (Box 67, Folder 14)
    Author: L. Kaufman
- Box: 67, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The "New" trades unionism, 1890; Publication (Box 67, Folder 15)
    Author: Tom Mann
- Box: 67, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Two classes in 1931, Publication (Box 67, Folder 16)
    Author: Emile Burns
- Box: 67, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The 2 nations: inequality in Britain today, 1973; Publication (Box 67, Folder 17)
    Author: Labour Research Department
- Box: 67, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: About wages, strikes, stewards, 1959; Publication (Box 67, Folder 18)
    Author: George Crane
- Box: 67, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Accounts of expenditure of wage-earning women and girls, 1911; Publication (Box 67, Folder 19)
    Author: Great Britain. Board of Trade
- Box: 67, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Adult education for co-operators, 1944; Publication (Box 67, Folder 20)
    Author: William Pascoe Watkings
- Box: 67, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Adult education for co-operators, 1982; Publication (Box 67, Folder 21)
    Author: Ahmad Ghotbi
- Box: 67, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Agreement: April 30th, 1931, Publication (Box 67, Folder 22)
    Author: Amalgamted Union of Dyers, Bleachers and Textile Workers (Great Britain)
- Box: 67, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The aims of labour, 1918; Publication (Box 67, Folder 23)
    Author: Arthur Henderson
- Box: 67, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: An account of the labour & socialist movement in Bristol, 1929; Publication (Box 67, Folder 24)
    Author: Samson Bryher
- Box: 67, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: An engineer looks at Russia, 1947; Publication (Box 67, Folder 25)
    Author: Wal Hannington
- Box: 67, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: An introduction to people and productivity, 1967; Publication (Box 67, Folder 26)
    Author: Alan Fox
- Box: 67, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: An open letter to a trade unionist, 1951; Publication (Box 67, Folder 27)
    Author: Harry Pollitt
- Box: 67, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: An urgent memorandum on production, 1942; Publication (Box 67, Folder 28)
    Author: Communist Party of Great Britain
- Box: 67, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Anti-labour legislations, 1924; Publication (Box 67, Folder 29)
    Author: William Thomas Colyer
- Box: 67, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Appeal on behalf of victimised & imprisoned Yorkshire Woollen Textile Strikers and their dependents, Publication (Box 67, Folder 30)
- Box: 67, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Are controls necessary?, 1945; Publication (Box 67, Folder 31)
    Author: Barbara Castle
- Box: 67, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Are you a worker?, Publication (Box 67, Folder 32)
    Author: Richard Stafford Cripps
- Box: 67, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Attack on the dockers, 1931; Publication (Box 67, Folder 33)
    Author: Dockers Minority Movement
- Box: 67, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Banks, prices & unemployment, 1925; Publication (Box 67, Folder 34)
    Author: John MacLeod
- Box: 67, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Barriers of the bureaucrats, 1929; Publication (Box 67, Folder 35)
    Author: D. Proudfoot
- Box: 67, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Behind German dreadnoughts, 1909; Publication (Box 67, Folder 36)
    Author: R.B. Suthers
- Box: 67, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The benefits of co-operation, 1900; Publication (Box 67, Folder 37)
    Author: George T. Arnold
- Box: 67, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 67, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: British imperialism; an outline of workers' conditions in the Colonies, 1927; Publication (Box 67, Folder 38)
    Author: National Minority Movement (Great Britain)
- Box: 67, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: British miners in Russia, 1950; Publication (Box 67, Folder 39)
    Author: British Soviet Friendship Society
- Box: 67, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 67, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: British steel at Britain's service, 1949; Publication (Box 67, Folder 40)
    Author: Labour Party (Great Britain)
- Box: 67, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: British trade unionists in Moscow, 1949; Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
    Author: Henry Levitt
- Box: 67, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Can Lloyd George do it?, 1929; Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
    Author: John Maynard Keynes
- Box: 67, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Can we conquer unemployment?, Publication (Box 67, Folder 43)
    Author: Peter H. Ady
- Box: 67, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 67, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Carr's bill and how to kill it, 1971; Publication (Box 67, Folder 44)
    Author: Bert Ramelson
- Box: 67, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 67, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: The case for higher wages, 1963; Publication (Box 67, Folder 45)
- Box: 67, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: The case of the Amble miners, 1913; Publication (Box 67, Folder 46)
    Author: Newburgh Lodge Committee
- Box: 67, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Catering wages bill, 1943; Publication (Box 67, Folder 47)
    Author: Ernest Bevin
- Box: 67, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 67, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Central Scotland: report of the Labour Party's Commission of Enquiry into the Distressed Areas, 1937; Publication (Box 67, Folder 48)
    Author: Labour Party (Gt. Brit.). Commission of Enquiry into the Distressed Areas
- Box: 67, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 67, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Centralised control of industry, 1943; Publication (Box 67, Folder 49)
    Author: Ian Mikardo
- Box: 67, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 67, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: The challenge of the cross of Christ to the business man, 1916; Publication (Box 67, Folder 50)
    Author: W. Stuart Macgowan
- Box: 67, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 67, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: The choice of a career, Publication (Box 67, Folder 51)
    Author: National Institute of Industrial Psychology (Great Britain)
- Box: 67, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 67, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Choice of employment and administration of unemployment insurance and assistance with respect to boys and girls under the age of 18, 1934; Publication (Box 67, Folder 52)
    Author: Great Britain. Ministry of Labour
- Box: 67, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 67, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Christianity and industrial problems, 1919; Publication (Box 67, Folder 53)
    Author: H.J. Graham
- Box: 67, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 67, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: The church and the labouring man, 1916; Publication (Box 67, Folder 54)
    Author: Alexander Irvine
- Box: 67, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 67, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: The church and the worker, 1938; Publication (Box 67, Folder 55)
    Author: Virginia M. Crawford
- Box: 67, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 67, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Civil liberty and the industrial worker, 1942; Publication (Box 67, Folder 56)
    Author: Angela Tuckett
- Box: 67, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 67, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Class against class, 1834-1934, Publication (Box 67, Folder 57)
    Author: Allen Hutt
- Box: 67, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 67, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Clear the lines, 1943; Publication (Box 67, Folder 58)
- Box: 67, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 67, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Clothing and textile trades, 1912; Publication (Box 67, Folder 59)
    Author: Lucy Wyatt Papworth
- Box: 67, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 67, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Clyde munitions workers, 1915; Publication (Box 67, Folder 60)
    Author: Great Britain. Ministry of Munitions
- Box: 67, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 67, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Coal & the nation: a square deal for miners, 1943; Publication (Box 67, Folder 61)
    Author: Arthur Horner
- Box: 67, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 67, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Coal & the nation: a square deal for miners, 1946; Publication (Box 67, Folder 62)
    Author: Common Wealth (Political Party)
- Box: 67, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 67, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: The coal industry: dangers of nationalisation, 1919; Publication (Box 67, Folder 63)
    Author: Harold Cox
- Box: 67, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 67, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: The coloured worker: what are the facts?, Publication (Box 67, Folder 64)
- Box: 67, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 67, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Communism and industrial peace, 1928; Publication (Box 67, Folder 65)
    Author: J.R. Campbell
- Box: 67, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 67, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Communism and the co-ops, 1935; Publication (Box 67, Folder 66)
    Author: William Gallacher
- Box: 67, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 67, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: The Communist Party and the trade unions, 1958; Publication (Box 67, Folder 67)
    Author: Finlay Hart
- Box: 67, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 67, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Competition v. co-operation, 1894; Publication (Box 67, Folder 68)
    Author: Oliver Lodge
- Box: 67, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 67, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Compulsory military service and industrial conscription, 1916; Publication (Box 67, Folder 69)
- Box: 67, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 67, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Conditions of service of conciliation grades (except locomotive staff), 1920; Publication (Box 67, Folder 70)
    Author: National Union of Railwaymen (Great Britain)
- Box: 67, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 67, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: The conflict of rights, 1919; Publication (Box 67, Folder 71)
    Author: A. Lyle Samuel
- Box: 67, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 67, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Constitution and national agreements relating to rates of pay & conditions of employment in the Narrow Fabrics Industry, 1967; Publication (Box 67, Folder 72)
    Author: Joint Industrial Council (U.S.)
- Box: 67, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 67, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Co-operation in Soviet Russia, 1942; Publication (Box 67, Folder 73)
    Author: Esther Henrotte
- Box: 67, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 67, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Co-operation in the Soviet Union, 1937; Publication (Box 67, Folder 74)
    Author: Joseph Reeves
- Box: 67, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 67, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: The co-operative employee, 1946; Publication (Box 67, Folder 75)
    Author: H. Afford
- Box: 67, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 67, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: The co-operative movement: a foundation for durable peace, 1945; Publication (Box 67, Folder 76)
    Author: John Riley
- Box: 67, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 67, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: The co-operative movement in the progress to socialism, 1927; Publication (Box 67, Folder 77)
    Author: Independent Labour Party (Great Britain). Co-operative Policy Commission
- Box: 67, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 67, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: A co-operative standard for women workers: annaul congress, June 1908, Publication (Box 67, Folder 78)
    Author: Women's Co-operative Guild
- Box: 67, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 67, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Co-operative storekeeping: a syllabus for discussion groups, Publication (Box 67, Folder 79)
    Author: W.P. Watkins
- Box: 67, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 67, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: The co-ops and labour, 1945; Publication (Box 67, Folder 80)
    Author: G.D.H. Cole
- Box: 67, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 67, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: The cost of living index number: method of compilation, 1944; Publication (Box 67, Folder 81)
- Box: 67, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 67, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Demobilisation and employment, 1944; Publication (Box 67, Folder 82)
    Author: Political and Economic Planning (Think tank)
- Box: 67, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 67, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Democracy and authority in the co-operative movement, 1953; Publication (Box 67, Folder 83)
- Box: 67, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 67, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Development of the education of wage-earners, 1917; Publication (Box 67, Folder 84)
    Author: Spurley Hey
- Box: 67, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 67, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Discrimination against coloured people, Publication (Box 67, Folder 85)
    Author: Mary Yates
- Box: 67, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 67, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: The distinction between joint-stockism and co-operation, Publication (Box 67, Folder 86)
    Author: Edward Vansittart Neale
- Box: 67, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 67, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: District societies: plans for development of Co-operative service, 1942; Publication (Box 67, Folder 87)
    Author: Co-operative Union Ltd.; Robert A. Palmer
- Box: 67, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 67, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Docks!: the fight for jobs, 1972; Publication (Box 67, Folder 88)
    Author: Bill Dunn
- Box: 67, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 67, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Does capital rob labour?, 1904; Publication (Box 67, Folder 89)
    Author: London Municipal Society
- Box: 67, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 67, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Draft resolution on organisation, 1934; Publication (Box 67, Folder 90)
    Author: National Unemployed Workers' Movement
- Box: 67, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 67, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Durham and the north east coast, 1937; Publication (Box 67, Folder 91)
    Author: Labour Party (Great Britain). Commission of Enquiry into the Distressed Areas
- Box: 67, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 67, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Election of assistant general secretary, 1954; Publication (Box 67, Folder 92)
    Author: Amalgamated Engineering Union
- Box: 67, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 67, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Election of national organiser: list of candidates with addresses, 1960; Publication (Box 67, Folder 93)
- Box: 67, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 67, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Employment after the war: a memorandum, 1945; Publication (Box 67, Folder 94)
    Author: Social Credit Co-ordinating Committee
- Box: 67, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 67, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Employing married women, 1961; Publication (Box 67, Folder 95)
    Author: Viola Klein
- Box: 67, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 67, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Employment for all, 1944; Publication (Box 67, Folder 96)
- Box: 67, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 67, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: The employment of women: suggestions to employers, 1941; Publication (Box 67, Folder 97)
    Author: Great Britain. Ministry of Labour and National Service
- Box: 67, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 67, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Employment policy, 1944; Publication (Box 67, Folder 98)
    Author: Great Britain. Office of the Minister of Reconstruction
- Box: 67, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 67, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: Employment relief: a letter to the Hon. Secretary of the Winchester Charity Organisation Society, 1905; Publication (Box 67, Folder 99)
    Author: Charles Stewart Loch
- Box: 67, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 67, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: End the ban: Communist Party members of the EETPU present the case for equal rights in their union, 1979; Publication (Box 67, Folder 100)
- Box: 67, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 67, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: The engineer looks ahead, 1952; Publication (Box 67, Folder 101)
    Author: Gilbert Hitchings
- Box: 67, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 67, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: The engineers' struggle, 1929; Publication (Box 67, Folder 102)
    Author: Jack Tanner
- Box: 67, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 67, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Enquiry into the conditions of domestic service, 1911; Publication (Box 67, Folder 103)
    Author: Women's Industrial Council (Great Britain)
- Box: 67, Folder: 104, Publication (Box 67, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: Equal pay for equal work, 1944; Publication (Box 67, Folder 104)
    Author: Tamara Rust
- Box: 67, Folder: 105, Publication (Box 67, Folder 105)
  - Item 1: Educational commentary, 1944; Publication (Box 67, Folder 105)
    Author: Marx Memorial Library and Workers' School; Daily Worker (London, England)
- Box: 67, Folder: 106, Publication (Box 67, Folder 106)
  - Item 1: Ergonomics, 1967; Publication (Box 67, Folder 106)
    Author: Reginald George Sell
- Box: 67, Folder: 107, Publication (Box 67, Folder 107)
  - Item 1: The ethical basis of the Labour movement, 1895; Publication (Box 67, Folder 107)
    Author: J.M. Wilson
- Box: 67, Folder: 108, Publication (Box 67, Folder 108)
  - Item 1: The evolution of industry, 1918; Publication (Box 67, Folder 108)
    Author: William McLaine
- Box: 67, Folder: 109, Publication (Box 67, Folder 109)
  - Item 1: Exhibition of labour trade union & democratic history, 1963; Publication (Box 67, Folder 109)
    Author: Colman Institute Redhill
- Box: 67, Folder: 110, Publication (Box 67, Folder 110)
  - Item 1: Explosion and underground fire, 1911; Publication (Box 67, Folder 110)
    Author: Thomas Richards
- Box: 67, Folder: 111, Publication (Box 67, Folder 111)
  - Item 1: The fair wages clause: an explanatory statement, 1934; Publication (Box 67, Folder 111)
    Author: Trades Union Congress
- Box: 67, Folder: 112, Publication (Box 67, Folder 112)
  - Item 1: The federation of trade unions, 1897; Publication (Box 67, Folder 112)
    Author: P.J. King; Robert Blatchford
- Box: 67, Folder: 113, Publication (Box 67, Folder 113)
  - Item 1: Fettering the workers, 1927; Publication (Box 67, Folder 113)
    Author: Trade Union Defence Committee
- Box: 67, Folder: 114, Publication (Box 67, Folder 114)
  - Item 1: A few historical notes on the Worshipful Company of Stationers, 1921; Publication (Box 67, Folder 114)
    Author: J.R. Riddell
- Box: 67, Folder: 115, Publication (Box 67, Folder 115)
  - Item 1: Fifty facts on public ownership, 1950; Publication (Box 67, Folder 115)
- Box: 67, Folder: 116, Publication (Box 67, Folder 116)
  - Item 1: For better factory laws, 1937; Publication (Box 67, Folder 116)
    Author: Helen Waddell
- Box: 67, Folder: 117, Publication (Box 67, Folder 117)
  - Item 1: For international trade union unity, 1935; Publication (Box 67, Folder 117)
- Box: 67, Folder: 118, Publication (Box 67, Folder 118)
  - Item 1: For the benefit of the people, 1960; Publication (Box 67, Folder 118)
    Author: Georgi Vasilyevich Perov
- Box: 67, Folder: 119, Publication (Box 67, Folder 119)
  - Item 1: Debate on Co-operative v. Private Trading: Monday, June 9th, 1947, Publication (Box 67, Folder 119)
    Author: London Co-operative Society Political Committee
- Box: 67, Folder: 120, Publication (Box 67, Folder 120)
  - Item 1: Forced labour, 1917; Publication (Box 67, Folder 120)
    Author: J.A. Hobson
- Box: 67, Folder: 121, Publication (Box 67, Folder 121)
  - Item 1: Forced labour in Russia, 1931; Publication (Box 67, Folder 121)
    Author: British Russian gazette and trade outlook
- Box: 67, Folder: 122, Publication (Box 67, Folder 122)